Don't start tidying.
不要开始整理房间
Please, Bingo, you have to keep playing or Dad will stop playing.
求你了  宾果继续玩游戏吧  不然爸爸也不玩了
I don't want to play anymore.
我不想再去玩了
Please?
求你了  好吗
No!
不行
Please.
求你了
No.
不行
Please, Bingo, I'll do anything.
求你了  宾果  我都听你的
No!
不行
OK.
好吧
Alright, I'll play.
好吧  我玩
Really? Yeah!
真的吗  太好了
But I want to be a crazy pillow.
但是我想当疯狂的枕头
OK.
好的
Yeah! Crazy pillow!
太棒了  疯狂的枕头
Hello, sir. I have a new pillow here for you.
您好先生  我为您准备了一个新枕头
Oh, thank you.
哦  谢谢
Don't worry, it's not a crazy pillow.
不要担心  这不是一个疯狂的枕头
Well, that's a plus.
哦  这是个附加的服务
My oh my, this is very comfortable and not wriggly at all.
哦  天哪  真舒服  一点都不会滑动
OK, well, I best go to sleep now. Night.
好的  我要睡觉了  晚安
Oh! Ah! Tickly nose. Hmm. That's odd.
哦  鼻子好痒  真奇怪
Hey! Pillow! Get back here!
嘿  枕头  快回来
Now stay there, pillow.
枕头  不要动
And where's my blanket?
我的毯子在哪
Ah, there it is!
哦  在这
Ah, that's better.
啊  现在好多了